Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online.

PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.  

**When do we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.  

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**Log Files:**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.

We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  

**We use cookies to:**

* Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
* Keep track of advertisements.
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.  

**Third-party disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.  

**Third-party links**  
We may include or offer third-party products or services on our website.  

Last Edited on 2017-01-22

#### Search

#### Recent Posts

#### [The Fascinating World of Asteroids: Cosmic Wanderers of the Solar System](https://intercelestial.com/the-fascinating-world-of-asteroids-cosmic-wanderers-of-the-solar-system/)

June 19, 2024

#### [Understanding Supernovae](https://intercelestial.com/understanding-supernovae/)

June 12, 2024

#### [Nebulae: Cosmic Canvases of Creation and Destruction](https://intercelestial.com/nebulae-cosmic-canvases-of-creation-and-destruction/)

March 18, 2024

#### [A Journey into the Depths of Black Holes](https://intercelestial.com/a-journey-into-the-depths-of-black-holes/)

December 16, 2023

#### [The Electromagnetic Spectrum](https://intercelestial.com/the-electromagnetic-spectrum/)

July 18, 2023

#### [Image Processing of Big Data](https://intercelestial.com/image-processing-of-big-data/)

July 4, 2023

#### [The SKA, Square Kilometer Array](https://intercelestial.com/the-ska-square-kilometer-array/)

June 18, 2023

#### [Astronautics](https://intercelestial.com/astronautics/)

June 1, 2023

#### [EHT, Event Horizon Telescope](https://intercelestial.com/eht-event-horizon-telescope/)

May 16, 2023

#### Tag Cloud

#### Categories

Categories Select Category Astrobiology Astronomy Astrophysics Cosmology History Radioastronomy Techno

#### Archives

Archives Select Month June 2024 March 2024 December 2023 July 2023 June 2023 May 2023 April 2023 March 2023 February 2023 January 2023 December 2022 November 2022 October 2022 September 2022 August 2022 July 2022 June 2022 May 2022 April 2022 March 2022 February 2022 January 2022 December 2021 November 2021 October 2021 September 2021 August 2021 July 2021 June 2021 May 2021 April 2021 March 2021 February 2021 January 2021 December 2020 November 2020 October 2020 August 2020 July 2020 June 2020 May 2020 March 2020 February 2020 January 2020 December 2019 November 2019 October 2019 August 2019 April 2019 January 2019 October 2018 August 2018 July 2018 May 2018 April 2018 March 2018 February 2018 January 2018 December 2017 November 2017 October 2017

#### Recent Comments

* asdasda on [The Birth of the Universe](https://intercelestial.com/the-birth-of-the-universe/comment-page-36/#comment-25097)
* [Herman](http://-/) on [Definition of Life Part III](https://intercelestial.com/definition-of-life-part-iii/comment-page-2/#comment-25094)
* [Herman](http://-/) on [Image Processing of Big Data](https://intercelestial.com/image-processing-of-big-data/comment-page-2/#comment-25093)
* Him on [The Birth of a Star](https://intercelestial.com/the-birth-of-a-star/comment-page-35/#comment-25092)
* dssds on [Our Galaxy](https://intercelestial.com/our-galaxy/comment-page-2/#comment-25091)

#### Get in Touch with Us

#### Search

#### Recent Posts

#### [The Fascinating World of Asteroids: Cosmic Wanderers of the Solar System](https://intercelestial.com/the-fascinating-world-of-asteroids-cosmic-wanderers-of-the-solar-system/)

June 19, 2024

#### [Understanding Supernovae](https://intercelestial.com/understanding-supernovae/)

June 12, 2024

#### [Nebulae: Cosmic Canvases of Creation and Destruction](https://intercelestial.com/nebulae-cosmic-canvases-of-creation-and-destruction/)

March 18, 2024

#### [A Journey into the Depths of Black Holes](https://intercelestial.com/a-journey-into-the-depths-of-black-holes/)

December 16, 2023

#### [The Electromagnetic Spectrum](https://intercelestial.com/the-electromagnetic-spectrum/)

July 18, 2023

#### [Image Processing of Big Data](https://intercelestial.com/image-processing-of-big-data/)

July 4, 2023

#### [The SKA, Square Kilometer Array](https://intercelestial.com/the-ska-square-kilometer-array/)

June 18, 2023

#### [Astronautics](https://intercelestial.com/astronautics/)

June 1, 2023

#### [EHT, Event Horizon Telescope](https://intercelestial.com/eht-event-horizon-telescope/)

May 16, 2023

#### Tag Cloud

#### Categories

Categories Select Category Astrobiology Astronomy Astrophysics Cosmology History Radioastronomy Techno

#### Archives

Archives Select Month June 2024 March 2024 December 2023 July 2023 June 2023 May 2023 April 2023 March 2023 February 2023 January 2023 December 2022 November 2022 October 2022 September 2022 August 2022 July 2022 June 2022 May 2022 April 2022 March 2022 February 2022 January 2022 December 2021 November 2021 October 2021 September 2021 August 2021 July 2021 June 2021 May 2021 April 2021 March 2021 February 2021 January 2021 December 2020 November 2020 October 2020 August 2020 July 2020 June 2020 May 2020 March 2020 February 2020 January 2020 December 2019 November 2019 October 2019 August 2019 April 2019 January 2019 October 2018 August 2018 July 2018 May 2018 April 2018 March 2018 February 2018 January 2018 December 2017 November 2017 October 2017

#### Recent Comments

* asdasda on [The Birth of the Universe](https://intercelestial.com/the-birth-of-the-universe/comment-page-36/#comment-25097)
* [Herman](http://-/) on [Definition of Life Part III](https://intercelestial.com/definition-of-life-part-iii/comment-page-2/#comment-25094)
* [Herman](http://-/) on [Image Processing of Big Data](https://intercelestial.com/image-processing-of-big-data/comment-page-2/#comment-25093)
* Him on [The Birth of a Star](https://intercelestial.com/the-birth-of-a-star/comment-page-35/#comment-25092)
* dssds on [Our Galaxy](https://intercelestial.com/our-galaxy/comment-page-2/#comment-25091)

#### Get in Touch with Us

Close

---------------------------------------------

© 2023 - Published with [WordPress](https://wordpress.org/)
